http://www.life-peace.org/policies

PoliciesThe Life & Peace Institute (LPI) takes personal data protection and privacy seriously and manages its users’ data in accordance with the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).When you sign-up to receive email updates or publications from us, you are asked to provide your name, email address, and specific background information about your interests. This personal data is shared with a third-party company based outside the European Union called MailChimp (owned by The Rocket Science Group LLC), whose system we use to send emails to our subscribers. Any data you provide is stored on secure servers by MailChimp.MailChimp is compliant with the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework, which means they are certified to receive data from LPI. For the purposes of GDPR, LPI is deemed the ‘Data Controller’ and MailChimp the ‘Data Processor’. To find out more about how MailChimp manages data, visit www.mailchimp.com/legal/privacy.When you use the life-peace.org website, your personal data is shared with a third-party company based outside the EU called Google Analytics (owned by Google LLC), whose software we use to track and analyse how people use and interact with our website. Any data collected is stored on secure servers by LPI and Google.Google Analytics is compliant with the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework, which means they are certified to receive data from LPI. For the purposes of GDPR, LPI is deemed the ‘Data Controller’ and Google Analytics the ‘Data Processor’. To find out more about how Google manages data, visit www.google.com/privacy.In 2018, in order to be fully compliant with the GDPR, the Life & Peace Institute officially adopted a full Privacy Policy. This GDPR-oriented policy will be reviewed on an annual basis by the Institute’s Director of Finance and Administration. To read more, please download the Life & Peace Institute’s Privacy Policy (2018).
